justinalexanderbridal.com 2013-09-30

# Wedding Dresses by Justin Alexander | Wedding Dress & Bridal Gown Designer | Privacy Policy

### 

This web site, which is located at [ **www.justinalexanderbridal.com**](http://www.justinalexanderbridal.com/)  (the “Site”), is published and maintained by Justin Alexander, with offices located at 711 Executive Boulevard, Suite G, Valley Cottage, New York. This Privacy Policy governs your access to and use of the Site and any other website, microsite, mobile device application, or Internet property owned, or operated by Justin Alexander, and related services (collectively with the Site, the "Justin Alexander Web Properties”). By visiting the Justin Alexander Web Properties, and/or using the related services, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy as they may be amended from time to time. As we update and expand our services, this Privacy Policy may change, so check back to this page from time to time. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and part of, the Justin Alexander  **Terms of Use** , which governs your use of the Justin Alexander Web Properties. The Justin Alexander Web Properties are intended for users who are located in the United States of America, and shall be interpreted under the laws of the United States.

**PURPOSE**

Your privacy is a serious matter to us. In order to make your visits to the Justin Alexander Web Properties and use of the related services as worthwhile as possible, we may ask you for Personal Information and we may collect certain information from your computer each time you visit us. "Personal Information" includes, for example, your name; home and/or business address; e-mail address; telephone, wireless and/or fax number; short message service or text message address or other wireless device address; instant messaging address; credit/debit card and other payment information; demographic information and/or other information that may identify you as an individual or allow online or offline contact with you as an individual. This Privacy Policy explains, in general, what Personal Information and other information is collected via the Justin Alexander Web Properties, how the information is used, and with whom we may share such information. Please take a few minutes to read our Privacy Policy so that you understand how Justin Alexander treats your information.

**RIGHT TO OPT OUT**

You have the right to "opt-out" of certain of our uses of your Personal Information. For example, at the time you are requested to provide Personal Information on the Justin Alexander Web Properties, you may have the opportunity to elect to, or not to: (1) receive correspondence from us, or (2) have your Personal Information shared with other entities for their marketing purposes. (We will not share, sell or trade your Personal Information with other for their marketing purposes without your permission. See the "Do we share Personal Information and Usage Information with others?" section below for more information about our data sharing practices.) You may also make this request by visiting our  **unsubscribe page  **. You may also opt-out of Justin Alexander's promotional e-mails by clicking on an opt-out link within the e-mail you receive.

Please understand that if you opt-out of receiving promotional correspondence from us, we may still contact you in connection with your relationship, activities, transactions, and communications with us. Also, a request to have us stop sharing your Personal Information with other entities for marketing purposes will only apply as of the date of your request, and we will not be responsible for any communications that you may receive from entities that received your Personal Information prior to such request. In these cases, please contact that entity directly.

**USER-PROVIDED INFORMATION**

We may collect Personal Information from users of our Justin Alexander Web Properties, for example, through such users' activities, transactions and completion of online forms on the Justin Alexander Web Properties. Such information is collected, for example, when users register or subscribe for accounts, electronic newsletters, or features on our Justin Alexander Web Properties, make online purchases, enter sweepstakes and contests, complete surveys, post materials, contribute to a chat room, bulletin board, list serve, blog, wiki or other open forum that we may make available on or through our Justin Alexander Web Properties, submit a comment or question to us using a "contact us" or similar feature on our Justin Alexander Web Properties, send us an e-mail, or in any other way submit Personal Information to us via our Justin Alexander Web Properties.

You may be able to send information about our products and services to your friends and family members through the Justin Alexander Web Properties by clicking on an "E-mail to Friend" or similar button on the Justin Alexander Web Properties or in an e-mail that we have sent you. In some of these cases (unless you simply forward our e-mail on your own), you may provide the name and e-mail address of your friend or family member to us. Such information will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy and applicable law. You may also be able to send an online card or message to a friend or family member, or send them a gift or gift certificate. If so, you may be required to provide us with your friend's or family member's Personal Information. Such information will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy and applicable law.

**USAGE INFORMATION**

We automatically collect anonymous Usage Information that does not identify an individual user ("Usage Information"). For example, each time you use the Justin Alexander Web Properties we automatically collect the type of Web browser you use, your operating system, your Internet Service Provider, your IP address, the pages you view, and the time and duration of your visits to such Justin Alexander Web Properties. We use this information to help us understand how people use Justin Alexander Web Properties, and to enhance the products and services we offer.

**COOKIES**

We may use "cookies" to keep, and sometimes track, analytics and information about you. Cookies are small data files that are sent to your browser or related software from a Web server and stored on your computer's or mobile device’s hard drive. Cookies track where you travel on the Justin Alexander Web Properties and what you look at and purchase. They may store the information in your shopping cart, and/or your username and/or password. A cookie may enable us to relate your use of the Justin Alexander Web Properties to other information about you, including your Personal Information. All of these purposes serve to improve and personalize your experience on the Justin Alexander Web Properties, to determine which areas and features of the Justin Alexander Web Properties are most popular, and to make improvements and updates to enhance the Justin Alexander Web Properties experience.

Most Web browsers can be set to inform you when a cookie has been sent to you and provide you with the opportunity to refuse that cookie. Additionally, if you have a Flash player installed on our computer, your Flash player can be set to reject or delete Flash cookies. However, refusing a cookie may, in some cases, preclude you from using, or negatively impact the display or function of, the Justin Alexander Web Properties or certain areas or features of the Justin Alexander Web Properties including preventing you from purchasing products from the Justin Alexander Web Properties.

**CLEAR GIFS**

We may use "clear GIFs" (aka "Web beacons" or "pixel tags") or similar technologies, in the Justin Alexander Web Properties and/or in our communications with you to enable us to know whether you have visited a Web page or received a message. A clear GIF is typically a one-pixel, transparent image (although it can be a visible image as well), located on a Web page or in an e-mail or other type of message, which is retrieved from a remote site on the Internet enabling the verification of an individual's viewing or receipt of a Web page or message. A clear gif may enable us to relate your viewing or receipt of a Web page or message to other information about you, including your Personal Information.

**IP ADDRESS AND CLICKSTREAM DATA**

Our server automatically collects data about your server's Internet address when you visit us. This information, known as an Internet Protocol address, or IP Address, is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider whenever you are on the Internet. When you request pages from the Justin Alexander Web Properties, our servers may log your IP Address and sometimes your domain name. Our servers may also record the referring page that linked you to us (e.g., another Web site or a search engine); the pages you visit on the Justin Alexander Web Properties; the Web site you visit after the Justin Alexander Web Properties; the ads you see and/or click on; your product interests and purchases; other information about the type of Web browser, computer, platform, related software and settings you are using; any search terms you have entered on the Justin Alexander Web Properties or a referral site; and other Web usage activity and data logged by our Web servers. We use this information for internal system administration, to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer the Justin Alexander Web Properties. Such information may also be used to gather broad demographic information, such as country of origin and Internet Service Provider. We may also link this information with your Personal Information. Any or all of these activities with regard to Web Site Usage Information may be performed on our behalf by our services providers.

**HOW IS THE PERSONAL INFORMATION USED?**

We will use the Personal Information you provide to the Justin Alexander Web Properties, for example, to respond to your requests and to provide you with our product and service offerings. For example, we will process your orders, respond to your requests and inquiries and provide you with the products, services and features offered on or through the Justin Alexander Web Properties. We may also use your Personal Information to help us develop and improve the Justin Alexander Web Properties, tailor the Justin Alexander Web Properties to your interests, and maintain our internal record keeping. We may match information collected from you through different means or at different times, including both Personal Information and Usage Information, and use such information along with information obtained from other sources, including third parties. In addition, we may send you notices (for example, in the form of e-mails, mailings, and the like), and otherwise correspond with you, about products, services, companies, promotions, contests and events, sponsored by us and others, that we think might interest you. Justin Alexander may offer electronic newsletters and e-mails as a service to our users. You will only receive a newsletter or promotional e-mail from Justin Alexander if you agree during registration, or during your other activities on or through the Justin Alexander Web Properties, or using our newsletter sign up form, to receive these items. Unsubscribe instructions are included in each electronic newsletter and e-mail. You may opt-out of receiving such notices from us by following the instructions in the Right to Opt Out section above. We may analyze user behavior as a measure of interest in, and use of, the Justin Alexander Web Properties and e-mails, both on an individual basis and in the aggregate.

**CO-SPONSORED CONTESTS, SWEEPSTAKES AND OFFERINGS**

Some of our contests, sweepstakes and other offerings that we may make available on or through the Justin Alexander Web Properties from time to time may be co-sponsored by another company. In those situations, the information we obtain from you in connection with such contest, sweepstake or offering may be shared with our co-sponsor, unless you instruct us not to by following the instructions in the Right to Opt Out section. In those situations, our co-sponsors will have the right to use your information for their own purposes, in accordance with their own policies. We are not responsible for how our co-sponsors may use your information.

**SERVICE PROVIDERS**

Currently, we use a third party partner to provide our e-commerce solution, and we may use other third party partners to help operate the Justin Alexander Web Properties and deliver our products and services. We may share your information with third party e-commerce solution partners, our affiliates, service providers, and other third parties that provide products or services for or through the Justin Alexander Web Properties or for our business (such as Justin Alexander Web Properties hosting or database hosting companies, address list hosting companies, e-mail service providers, analytics companies, distribution companies, fulfillment companies, wireless device applications, and other similar service providers that use such information on our behalf). We require our service providers to maintain the confidentiality of your Personal Information.

**AGGREGATE STATISTICS**

We may disclose aggregate statistics regarding user behavior as a measure of interest in, and use of, the Justin Alexander Web Properties and e-mails to third parties in the form of aggregate data, such as overall patterns or demographic reports that do not describe or identify any individual user. Aggregate information is non-personally identifiable/anonymous information about you, such as age, gender, types of products purchased, pages you access most frequently or search terms you enter. Aggregate information is used in a collective manner, and no single person can be identified by that compiled information. For example, the number of people who visit [ **www.justinalexanderbridal.com**](http://www.justinalexanderbridal.com/) who are 25 years of age is aggregate information that does not personally identify a specific user.

**LEGALLY COMPELLED DISCLOSURES**

We may disclose user information to government authorities, and to other third parties when compelled to do so by government authorities, at our discretion, or otherwise as required by law in our good faith belief, including but not limited to in response to court orders and subpoenas and as otherwise required in connection with a judicial or government proceeding or legal process. We also may disclose user information when we have reason to believe that someone is causing injury to or interference with our rights or property, other users of the Justin Alexander Web Properties, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. Justin Alexander cooperates with law enforcement inquiries and other third parties to enforce laws, intellectual property rights and other rights.

**WIRELESS ADDRESSES**

If the email address you provide to us is a wireless email address, you agree to receive messages at such address from Justin Alexander (unless and until you have elected not to receive such messages by following the instructions in the Right to Opt Out section above). You understand that your wireless carrier's standard rates apply to these messages, and that you may change your mind at any time by following the instructions in the Right to Opt Out section above. You represent that you are the owner or authorized user of the wireless device on which messages will be received, and that you are authorized to approve the applicable charges.

**YOUR ACCESS RIGHTS You may review the Personal Information that is stored in your user account on [ **www.justinalexanderbridal.com**](http://www.justinalexanderbridal.com/)  by logging in at  **"My Account"**  or by calling our customer service department at 1-845-369-6631. We will send you a copy of the Personal Information we have on file in your user account (if any). You may provide us new or updated information at any time. We will endeavor to respond to your request to access, update or delete your information as soon as practicable. Before we are able to provide you with any information, correct any inaccuracies or delete any information, however, we may ask you to verify your identity and to provide other details to help us to respond to your request.

**SECURITY**

Protecting your information is a priority for Justin Alexander Justin Alexander will take reasonable steps to protect the security and integrity of all Personal Information provided to the Justin Alexander Web Properties. For example, we use industry standard Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to protect the security of your sensitive online transactions. However, due to the inherent nature of the Internet as an open global communications vehicle, we cannot guarantee that information, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our system or otherwise in our care, will be absolutely safe from intrusion by others, such as hackers. No transmission of data over the Internet is guaranteed to be completely secure. It may be possible for third parties not under the control of Justin Alexander to intercept or access transmissions or private communications unlawfully. While we strive to protect your personal information, Justin Alexander cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. Any such transmission is done at your own risk.

If you  **contact us**  by e-mail, you should be aware that your transmission might not be secure. A third party could view information you send by these methods in transit.

You may be able to create an account on the Justin Alexander Web Properties with a username and password. If so, you are responsible for maintaining the strict confidentiality of your account password, and you shall be responsible for any access to or use of the Justin Alexander Web Properties by you or any person or entity using your password, whether or not such access or use has been authorized by or on behalf of you, and whether or not such person or entity is your employee or agent. You agree to (a) immediately notify Justin Alexander of any unauthorized use of your password or account or any other breach of security, and (b) ensure that you exit from your account at the end of each session. It is your sole responsibility to control the dissemination and use of your password, control access to and use of your account, and notify Justin Alexander when you desire to cancel your account on the Justin Alexander Web Properties. We will not be responsible or liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to comply with this provision, and you agree to indemnify and hold harmless Justin Alexander for any improper, unauthorized or illegal use of your account.

We will have no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors or unauthorized acts of third parties during or after transmission.

In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your Personal Information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you of that development. If a notification is appropriate, we would endeavor to do so as promptly as possible under the circumstances, and, to the extent we have your e-mail address, we may notify you by e-mail. You consent to our use of e-mail as a means of such notification.

**PHISHING**

With identity theft a continuing problem, it has become increasingly common for unauthorized individuals purporting to represent a legitimate company such as a bank or on-line merchant, to send e-mail messages to consumers requesting that the consumer provide personal, often sensitive information. Sometimes, the domain name of the e-mail address from which the e-mail appears to have been sent, and the domain name of the web site requesting such information, appears to be the domain name of a legitimate, trusted company. In reality, such sensitive information is received by an unauthorized individual to be used for purposes of identity theft. This illegal activity is known as "phishing."

If you receive an e-mail or other correspondence requesting that you provide any sensitive information (including your Justin Alexander Web Properties password or credit/debit card information) via e-mail or to a web site that does not seem to be affiliated with the Justin Alexander Web Properties, or that otherwise seems suspicious to you, please do not provide such information, and report such request to us by calling 1-845-369-6631.

**CHILDREN AND PRIVACY**

Justin Alexander is concerned about the safety of children when they use the Internet. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time with their children online and to be familiar with the sites their children visit. We will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent when legally required. If we become aware that a customer is under the age of 13 and has registered without the legally required prior verifiable parental consent, we will remove his or her personally identifiable registration information from our files.

Information posted to message boards, chat areas, club and home pages are available to the general public. Please use caution when posting any such information. Users under the age of 18 should be particularly careful not to provide any personally identifying information while using chat rooms, message boards, or any other public forums. Users of chat areas, message boards, or any other public forums must follow acceptable standards of behavior when posting messages online. Justin Alexander reserves the right to, but is not obligated to, refuse or delete any content that in our sole discretion is considered inappropriate.

**CONSENT TO PROCESSING**

The Justin Alexander Web Properties are hosted and operated in the United States, pursuant to United States law. By providing Personal Information to the Justin Alexander Web Properties, you understand and consent to the collection, maintenance, processing and transfer of such information in and to the United States and other countries and territories.

**THIRD PARTY "LINKED-TO" WEB SITES**

When you are on the Justin Alexander Web Properties you may have the opportunity to visit, or link to, other sites not operated by Justin Alexander. These sites may collect Personal Information about you. Justin Alexander does not control sites that are operated by these entities and is not responsible for the information practices of these sites. This Privacy Policy does not address the information practices of those other Web sites. 

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

Justin Alexander reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy, or any other of our policies or practices, at any time, and will notify users of the Justin Alexander Web Properties by posting such changed or updated Privacy Policy on this page. Any changes or updates will be effective immediately upon posting to [ **www.justinalexanderbridal.com**](http://www.justinalexanderbridal.com/). Your continued use of the Justin Alexander Web Properties constitutes your agreement to abide by the Privacy Policy as changed. Under certain circumstances (for example, if we would like to use your Personal Information in a manner different from that stated in our Privacy Policy at the time of collection), we may also elect to notify you of changes or updates to our Privacy Policy by additional means, such as by sending you an e-mail.

**CONTACT US**

If you have any questions or comments regarding our privacy practices, you may  **contact us**  or call 1-845-369-6631.

Effective Date: December 1, 2011

This is the web site of  **Justin Alexander Bridal.**

POSTAL ADDRESS  
711 Executive Blvd, Suite G, Valley Cottage, NY 10989

EMAIL ADDRESS  
info-us@justinalexanderbridal.com

TELEPHONE   
1 845.369.6631

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes the consumer's domain name and e-mail address (where possible).

We collect the domain name and e-mail address (where possible) of visitors to our Web page, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, the e-mail addresses of those who make postings to our chat areas, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.

The information we collect is used for internal review and is then discarded, used to improve the content of our Web page, used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor, used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site.

With respect to cookies: We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site .

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address. If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number.
